<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Solution</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable1_">Fable1_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_1_text">A Fox was boasting to a Cat of its clever devices for escaping its enemies.\n

"I have a whole bag of tricks," he said, "which contains a hundred ways of escaping my enemies."

"I have only one," said the Cat; "but I can generally manage with that."

Just at that moment they heard the cry of a pack of hounds coming towards them, and the Cat immediately scampered up a tree and hid herself in the boughs.

"This is my plan," said the Cat. "What are you going to do?" \n

The Fox thought first of one way, then of another, and while he was debating the hounds came nearer and nearer, and at last the Fox in his confusion was caught up by the hounds and soon killed by the huntsmen.\n

        Miss Puss, who had been looking on, said: "Better one safe way than a hundred on which you cannot reckon"</string>

    <string name="title_activity_fable2_">Fable2_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_2_text">It happened that a Fisher, after fishing all day, caught only a little fish.

    "Pray, let me go, master," said the Fish. "I am much too small for your eating just now.

    If you put me back into the river I shall soon grow, then you can make a fine meal off me."

    "Nay, nay, my little Fish," said the Fisher, "I have you now. I may not catch you hereafter."</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable3_">Fable3_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_3_text">One hot summers day a Fox was strolling through an orchard till he came to a bunch of Grapes just ripening on a vine which had been trained over a lofty branch. \n

"Just the thing to quench my thirst," quoth he.

Drawing back a few paces, he took a run and a jump, and just missed the bunch.\n\n

Turning round again with a One, Two, Three, he jumped up, but with no greater success.

Again and again he tried after the tempting morsel, but at last had to give it up, and walked away with his nose in the air, saying:

"I am sure they are sour."</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable4_">Fable4_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_4_text">The Frogs were living as happy as could be in a marshy swamp that just suited them; they went splashing about caring for nobody and nobody troubling with them.

But some of them thought that this was not right, that they should have a king and a proper constitution, so they determined to send up a petition to Jove to give them what they wanted. \n

"Mighty Jove," they cried, "send unto us a king that will rule over us and keep us in order."Jove laughed at their croaking, and threw down into the swamp a huge Log, which came down splashing into the swamp.

The Frogs were frightened out of their lives by the commotion made in their midst, and all rushed to the bank to look at the horrible monster; but after a time, seeing that it did not move, one or two of the boldest of them ventured out towards the Log, and even dared to touch it; still it did not move.\n

Then the greatest hero of the Frogs jumped upon the Log and commenced dancing up and down upon it, thereupon all the Frogs came and did the same; and for some time the Frogs went about their business every day without taking the slightest notice of their new King Log lying in their midst.\n

But this did not suit them, so they sent another petition to Jove, and said to him, "We want a real king; one that will really rule over us."

Now this made Jove angry, so he sent among them a big Stork that soon set to work gobbling them all up.

Then the Frogs repented when too late.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable5_">Fable5_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_5_text">A Horse and an Ass were travelling together, the Horse prancing along in its fine trappings, the Ass carrying with difficulty the heavy weight in its panniers.

"I wish I were you," sighed the Ass; "nothing to do and well fed, and all that fine harness upon you."\n

Next day, however, there was a great battle, and the Horse was wounded to death in the final charge of the day.

His friend, the Ass, happened to pass by shortly afterwards and found him on the point of death.

"I was wrong," said the Ass: "Better humble security than gilded danger"The Lion and the Fox went hunting together.

The Lion, on the advice of the Fox, sent a message to the Ass, proposing to make an alliance between their two families.

The Ass came to the place of meeting, overjoyed at the prospect of a royal alliance. \n\n

But when he came there the Lion simply pounced on the Ass, and said to the Fox:

"Here is our dinner for to-day. Watch you here while I go and have a nap. Woe betide you if you touch my prey."

The Lion went away and the Fox waited; but finding that his master did not return, ventured to take out the brains of the Ass and ate them up.

When the Lion came back he soon noticed the absence of the brains, and asked the Fox in a terrible voice:

"What have you done with the brains?"

"Brains, your Majesty! it had none, or it would never have fallen into your trap."</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable6_">Fable6_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_6_text">A Hare was very popular with the other beasts who all claimed to be her friends.

But one day she heard the hounds approaching and hoped to escape them by the aid of her many Friends.

So, she went to the horse, and asked him to carry her away from the hounds on his back.

But he declined, stating that he had important work to do for his master.

"He felt sure," he said, "that all her other friends would come to her assistance." \n\n

 She then applied to the bull, and hoped that he would repel the hounds with his horns.

The bull replied: "I am very sorry, but I have an appointment with a lady; but I feel sure that our friend the goat will do what you want."

The goat, however, feared that his back might do her some harm if he took her upon it.\n\n

The ram, he felt sure, was the proper friend to apply to.

So she went to the ram and told him the case.

The ram replied: "Another time, my dear friend. \n I do not like to interfere on the present occasion, as hounds have been known to eat sheep as well as hares."

The Hare then applied, as a last hope, to the calf, who regretted that he was unable to help her, as he did not like to take the responsibility upon himself, as so many older persons than himself had declined the task.

By this time the hounds were quite near, and the Hare took to her heels and luckily escaped</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable7">Fable7</string>
    <string name="fable_7_text">A Lion had come to the end of his days and lay sick unto death at the mouth of his cave, gasping for breath.\n

The animals, his subjects, came round him and drew nearer as he grew more and more helpless.

When they saw him on the point of death they thought to themselves: "Now is the time to pay off old grudges."

So the Boar came up and drove at him with his tusks; then a Bull gored him with his horns; still the Lion lay helpless before them: so the Ass, feeling quite safe from danger, came up, and turning his tail to the Lion kicked up his heels into his face.

"This is a double death" growled the Lion.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable8">Fable8</string>
    <string name="fable_8_text">A stag saw his shadow reflected in the water, and greatly admired the size of his horns, but felt angry with himself for having such weak feet.

While he was thus contemplating himself, a Lion appeared at the pool.

The Stag betook himself to flight, and kept himself with ease at a safe distance from the Lion, until he entered a wood and became entangled with his horns.

The Lion quickly came up with him and caught him.

When too late he thus reproached himself:

"Woe is me! How have I deceived myself! \n These feet which would have saved me I despised, and I gloried in these antlers which have proved my destruction."</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable9_">Fable9_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_9_text">A young Man had been caught in a daring act of theft and had been condemned to be executed for it.

He expressed his desire to see his Mother, and to speak with her before he was led to execution, and of course this was granted.

When his Mother came to him he said: "I want to whisper to you," and when she brought her ear near him, he nearly bit it off. \nAll the bystanders were horrified, and asked him what he could mean by such brutal and inhuman conduct.

"It is to punish her," he said. "When I was young I began with stealing little things, and brought them home to Mother. Instead of rebuking and punishing me, she laughed and said: It will not be noticed. It is because of her that I am here to-day."

"He is right, woman," said the Priest; "the Lord hath said: Train up a child in the way he should go; and when he is old he will not depart therefrom."</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable10_">Fable10_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_10_text">A Thief came in the night to break into a house. He brought with him several slices of meat, that he might pacify the House-dog, so that he should not alarm his master by barking.

As the Thief threw him the pieces of meat, the Dog said:

"If you think to stop my mouth, to relax my vigilance, or even to gain my regard by these gifts, you will be greatly mistaken.\n
        This sudden kindness at your hands will only make me more watchful, lest under these unexpected favors to myself you have some private ends to accomplish for your own benefit, and for my master's injury.
        Besides, this is not the time that I am usually fed, which makes me all the more suspicions of your intentions."</string>
</resources>
